♪I'll go with you to see your favorite flower in spring♪
♪سأذهب معك لرؤية زهرتك ​​المفضلة في الربيع♪
♪I'll treat you to your favorite ice cream in summer♪
♪ سأقدم لك الآيس كريم المفضل لديك في الصيف ♪
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك تحت المطر عندما تكون حزيناً في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني لك رجل ثلج في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ أنت فقط من تستطيع الحصول على رومانسيتي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ الجميع ثانوي ♪
♪I like your every smile and frown♪
♪ أحب كل ابتسامتك وعبوسك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪I want to take you to watch the stars♪
♪أريد أن آخذك لمشاهدة النجوم♪
♪Please♪
♪من فضلك♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪ دعني أعتني بك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪When it's cold, hide in my arms♪
♪ عندما يكون الجو بارداً، إختبئ بين ذراعي ♪
♪Drive all your sadness♪
♪ تخلص من كل حزنك ♪
♪Completely away♪
♪بعيد تمامًا♪
=Falling In Love With Me= =Episode 4=
=الوقوع في حبي= =الحلقة 4=
You like me so much?
أنت تحبني كثيرا؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I'll give you a chance.
سأعطيك فرصة.
Pass my music theory test with full marks
اجتياز اختبار نظرية الموسيقى الخاص بي بعلامات كاملة
and I'll agree.
وسأوافق.
Y-Y-You're making it hard for me.
YY-أنت تجعل الأمر صعبًا بالنسبة لي.
Not even willing to put in a little effort
ولا حتى على استعداد لبذل القليل من الجهد
and you say you like me?
وتقول أنك معجب بي؟
So it's not genuine.
لذلك فهي ليست حقيقية.
Miss Tong,
الآنسة تونغ،
I won't play your game.
لن ألعب لعبتك.
Well.
حسنًا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Why is he leaving?
لماذا يغادر؟
Tang Yutong,
تانغ يوتونغ,
I agree.
أنا موافق.
I'm definitely not going to give up.
أنا بالتأكيد لن أستسلم.
- Good!
- جيد!  - جيد!
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
Check.
يفحص.
(Give me a kiss, can you?)
(أعطني قبلة، هل تستطيع؟)
You're so handsome.
انت وسيم جدا.
How can you be so hardhearted?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون قاسي القلب إلى هذا الحد؟
If you have time,
اذا لديك وقت،
go to study.
اذهب للدراسة.
(Basic Music Theories)
(نظريات الموسيقى الأساسية)
I am a senior singer-songwriter.
أنا مغني وكاتب أغاني كبير.
Why should I learn this?
لماذا يجب أن أتعلم هذا؟
Have you heard Tong Yuxin's new song?
هل سمعت أغنية تونغ يوكسين الجديدة؟
What a piece of garbage.
ما قطعة من القمامة.
I can't believe I liked her.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنني أحببتها.
I was simply blind,
لقد كنت ببساطة أعمى،
no, deaf.
لا، أصم.
Yeah.
نعم.
Unmusical.
غير رنان.
Cracking voice.
صوت تكسير.
Even my grandma sings better.
حتى جدتي تغني بشكل أفضل.
And her songs
وأغانيها
are words like "one, two, three" and "ah".
هي كلمات مثل "واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة" و"آه".
Even a pupil could write those
حتى التلميذ يمكنه كتابة تلك
and she claims
وهي تدعي
to be a songwriter.
ليكون كاتب الأغاني.
No wonder she never shows her face.
لا عجب أنها لا تظهر وجهها أبدا.
Singing these songs?
غناء هذه الأغاني؟
She must find it shameful.
يجب أن تجد ذلك مخزيًا.
Who knows?
من تعرف؟
Maybe she looks ugly.
ربما تبدو قبيحة.
(Library)
(مكتبة)
Just now,
الآن،
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Only you can help yourself.
أنت فقط تستطيع مساعدة نفسك.
Mr. Tang,
السيد.  تانغ،
will you really return my necklace to me
هل ستعيدين لي قلادتي حقاً؟
if I get full marks on your test?
إذا حصلت على العلامات الكاملة في الاختبار الخاص بك؟
I walk the talk.
أنا أمشي الحديث.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's see.
دعنا نرى.
I will keep my promise.
سوف احفظ وعدي.
Now playing, as requested by Mr. Wang,
نلعب الآن، بناءً على طلب السيد وانغ،
the new song by Mr. Tang Yutong,
الأغنية الجديدة للسيد تانغ يوتونغ،
"The First Snow."
"الثلج الاول."
♪It's the fallen leaves everywhere It's the counter-clockwise clock♪
♪ إنها الأوراق المتساقطة في كل مكان، إنها عقارب الساعة عكس اتجاه عقارب الساعة ♪
♪It's the pure white flowers slipping into my collar♪
♪إنها الزهور البيضاء النقية التي تنزلق إلى ياقتي♪
Mr. Tang.
السيد.  تانغ.
- Tang Yutong, we like you.
- تانغ يوتونغ، نحن نحبك - تانغ يوتونغ، نحن نحبك.
♪Ayo, I'm explaining why you prolly never see me♪
♪ آيو، أنا أشرح لك سبب عدم رؤيتي أبدًا ♪
- Tang Yutong!
- تانغ يوتونغ - تانغ يوتونغ!
I like you, Tang Yutong.
أنا معجب بك، تانغ يوتونغ.
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك تحت المطر عندما تكون حزيناً في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني لك رجل ثلج في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ أنت فقط من تستطيع الحصول على رومانسيتي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ الجميع ثانوي ♪
- Tang Yutong!
- تانغ يوتونغ - تانغ يوتونغ!
Watch out!
احترس!
(Here's a bonus clip.)
(إليك مقطع إضافي.)
=Falling In Love With Me=
=الوقوع في الحب معي=
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
24 hours a day.
24 ساعة في اليوم.
You spend 18 hours primping.
تقضي 18 ساعة في التحضير.
It's better to spend
من الأفضل أن تنفق
the time on music.
الوقت على الموسيقى.
This season's new outfit is nice.
الزي الجديد لهذا الموسم جميل.
How much longer?
كم تبقى من الوقت؟
Isn't it just to handle a music teacher?
أليس الأمر مجرد التعامل مع مدرس الموسيقى؟
Do you need to be so serious?
هل يجب أن تكون جادًا جدًا؟
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
He is not an ordinary music teacher.
إنه ليس مدرس موسيقى عادي.
He's handsome,
انه وسيم،
and what else?
وماذا ايضا؟
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪In the few weeks after breaking up♪
♪ في الأسابيع القليلة بعد الانفصال ♪
♪I restrain myself from missing you♪
♪ أنا أمنع نفسي من أن أفتقدك ♪
♪Like a chronic disease, it comes and goes♪
♪ مثل المرض المزمن، يأتي ويذهب ♪
♪Maybe I'm to blame for loving too deeply♪
♪ ربما أنا الملام على الحب العميق ♪
♪Will time heal the heartbreak♪
♪ هل الزمن سيشفي حسرة القلب ♪
♪Or will it make it more painful♪
♪ أم أنه سيجعل الأمر أكثر إيلاما ♪
♪Missing you is an incurable disease♪
♪ اشتياقك داء لا شفاء منه ♪
♪Yet now I think of you again♪
♪ والآن أفكر فيك مرة أخرى ♪
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪I am not afraid of lonely nights♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الليالي المنعزلة♪
♪Everyone knows it is a lie♪
♪ الجميع يعلم أنها كذبة ♪
♪I don't want to bear the pain of missing again♪
♪ لا أريد أن أتحمل ألم الافتقاد مرة أخرى ♪
♪Can you please let me go♪
♪هل يمكنك أن تسمح لي بالذهاب ♪
♪The carriage of time won't stop♪
♪ لن تتوقف عربة الزمن ♪
♪I'm sorry. I can't be the person you're with for the rest of your life♪
♪ أنا آسف.  لا أستطيع أن أكون الشخص الذي أنت معه لبقية حياتك ♪